<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fast on LiveCollage</title>
    <link>http://donker008.github.io/tags/fast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fast on LiveCollage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 14:45:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://donker008.github.io/tags/fast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>App Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://donker008.github.io/privacy/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 14:45:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://donker008.github.io/privacy/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We think your online privacy is very important and we’ll do our best to protect it. This web page describes the type of personal information we collect from you and what we do with it. We hope you find it useful in deciding whether or not to share information about yourself with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, we would like to stress that we follow the privacy requirements provided by Facebook for all applications that wish to participate in the Facebook ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Information We Used&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you authorize app to access your Facebook account, we collect and store some information about you, such as your Facebook identifier which we use to save your photo frame or collage or image to your  photo album. The full list of information we collect is presented to you on the Facebook authorization screen.
Policy Changes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because we continually try to add useful new features to the app, we might start collecting information beyond what has been described in this policy. In this case, we will update this policy promptly so you know what has been changed. Please do check back frequently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More Information&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do our best to protect your privacy and to keep our privacy policy easy to understand. If you have further questions regarding your privacy, please contact us at: livecollage.us@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;July 2, 2012&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://donker008.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 14:07:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://donker008.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mission of &lt;strong&gt;Click2Mobile&lt;/strong&gt; is to help you make mobile experience simpler &amp;amp; easier! If you have any questions &amp;amp; suggestions, please feel free to contact us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:livecollage.us@gmail.com&#34;&gt;livecollage.us@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast - sketch collage &amp; music video maker</title>
      <link>http://donker008.github.io/post/FAST/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 23:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://donker008.github.io/post/FAST/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://j.mp/fastcollage&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://7xp3b4.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/180fast.png&#34; alt=&#34;Fast&#34; title=&#34;Fast Collage&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
Make your photos into fun collage and music video in SKETCH style with GIF,Music,Artwork,Text!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remixing your own photos into fun collage &amp;amp; video and sharing them with your friends. Smash bored collage with our unique SKETCH layouts. Live your collage with GIF, Music, Artwork,Text!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast makes it easy and fun to create hilarious, creative collages!
Choose photos from your camera roll. Pick the layout you like best, then edit it to make it your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast&amp;rsquo;s smooth, intuitive process gives you complete creative control. Tap to mirror, flip or replace images, hold and drag to swap them, pinch to zoom in or out. Fast&amp;rsquo;s give your endless creativities to spice up your photos with Music,Funny GIF,Text, Cute Artwork, Retouch Effect!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s never been easier to make every moment worth a memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://7xp3b4.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/creative300.png&#34; alt=&#34;creative&#34; /&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://j.mp/fastcollage&#34;&gt;GET it for Free from Appstore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>